<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Salesforce to Workday Account to Customer Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">

As an admin I want to migrate Salesforce accounts to Workday customers.

This template should serve as a foundation for the process of migrating accounts from Salesforce, where you can specify the filtering criteria 
and desired behavior when the corresponding Customer already exists in Workday.

As implemented, this template leverages the Mule batch module.
The batch job is divided into *Process* and *On Complete* stages.

Firstly the template queries all the existing Accounts at Salesforce that match the filtering criteria.
In the *Process* stage, the template queries the Workday for already existing customers based on the Salesforce IDs retrieved before the batch processing.
The customers get inserted or updated in the Workday system based on the results of these queries.
Lastly, the information about the migration results is sent to pre-configured e-mail recipient and output to the console as well.

	    </section>
		<section id="considerations">

There are certain pre-requisites that must be considered to run this template. 
All of them deal with the preparations in both source and destination systems, that must be made for the template to run smoothly. 
**Failing to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**

		</section>
		<section id="wdayf_dst">

When creating new Workday customer, one of existing customer categories must be chosen. In order to do this, this template uses lookup table with pre-defined mappings between Salesforce data (Industry) and Workday Customer Category ID.
Workday customer categories can be user defined, therefore the mapping must be edited by user manually before running this template.

To view all the Workday Customer Categories, please type "customer categories" into search field in Workday system and select Customer Categories report.
In the report you should see all the customer categories available. Select Integration IDs -&gt; View Integration IDs from available actions of each customer 
category and update the function *industryToCustomerCategoryMapping* in the template's DataWeave component 'Prepare put customer request' manually.
The default customer category ID can be edited inside the same DataWeave component in the row where customer category ID is set. This category will be used if the source Account's Industry 
value does not match any defined mappings in the function.

		</section>
		<section id="run_it">

Whichever way you choose to run this template, this this is an example of the output you'll see after browse toting the HTTP endpoint:

&lt;pre&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Batch Process initiated&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;b&gt;ID:&lt;/b&gt;6eea3cc6-7c96-11e3-9a65-55f9f3ae584e&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Records to be processed: &lt;/b&gt;3&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Started execution on: &lt;/b&gt;Mon Jan 25 10:08:16 CET 2016
&lt;/pre&gt;

		</section>
		<section id="running_on_cloudhub">

Once your app is all set up and started, supposing you choose as domain name `sfdcaccountmigration` to trigger the use 
case you just need to browse to `http://sfdcaccountmigration.cloudhub.io/migrateaccounts` and report will be sent to the emails configured.

		</section>
		<section id="running_on_standalone">

After this, to trigger the use case you just need to browse to the local HTTP connector with the port you configured in your file. If this is, for instance, `9090` then you should browse to: `http://localhost:9090/migrateaccounts` and this will output a summary report and send it in the e-mail.

		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">

**Application Configuration**

 + http.port `9090`
 + page.size `200`

**Salesforce Connector Configuration**

 + sfdc.username `bob.dylan@orga`
 + sfdc.password `DylanPassword123`
 + sfdc.securityToken `avsfwCUl7apQs56Xq2AKi3X`

**Workday Connector Configuration**

 + wdayf.username `joan`
 + wdayf.tenant `acme_pt1`
 + wdayf.password `joanPass123`
 + wdayf.host `your_impl-cc.workday.com`
 
 + wdayf.country `USA`
 + wdayf.state `USA-CA`
 + wdayf.postalCode `90001`
 + wdayf.city `San Francisco`
 + wdayf.street `Main Street 123`
 + wdayf.phone `123-4567`

**SMTP Services Configuration**

 + smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
 + smtp.port `587`
 + smtp.user `gmail_user`
 + smtp.password `gmail_password`

**Email Details**

 + mail.from `batch.migrateaccounts.migration%40mulesoft.com`
 + mail.to `your.email@example.com`
 + mail.subject `Batch Job Finished Report`

		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">

Salesforce imposes limits on the number of API Calls that can be made. However, we make API call to Salesforce only once during migration, so this is not something to worry about. 

		</section>
		<section id="default_endpoints_xml">

This is the file where you will find the inbound side of your integration app.
This Template has only an HTTP Listener as the way to trigger the use case.

**HTTP Listener Connector** - Start Report Generation

+ `${http.port}` is set as a property to be defined either on a property file or in CloudHub environment variables.
+ The path configured by default is `migrateaccounts` and you are free to change for the one you prefer.
+ The host name for all endpoints in your CloudHub configuration should be defined as `localhost`. CloudHub will then route requests from your application domain URL to the endpoint.

		</section>
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">

Functional aspect of the template is implemented on this XML, directed by one flow responsible of excecuting the logic.
For the pourpose of this particular template the *mainFlow* just excecutes a batch job which handles all the migration logic.
This flow has Error handling that points to errorHandlingFlow defined in *errorHandling.xml* file.

		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>